{
	"sections": [
		{
			"name": "Quantitative Methods",
			"children": [
				{
					"name": "Required Rate of Return",
					"children": [
						{
							"name": "Nominal Risk-Free Rate",
							"content": {
								"id": 1,
								"question": "nominal risk-free rate = real risk-free rate + expected inflation rate",
								"answer": "15",
								"tolerance": 0.01,
								"seed": 4235759
							}
						},
						{
							"name": "Required Interest Rate",
							"content": {
								"id": "2",
								"question": "required interest rate = nominal risk-free rate + default risk premium + liquidity, premium + maturity risk premium",
								"answer": "15",
								"tolerance": 0.01,
								"seed": 2548976
							}
						}
					]
				},
				{
					"name": "Effective Annual Rates",
					"content": {
						"id": "L1EffAnn",
						"question": "\\[EAR = (1 + periodic rate)^m - 1\\]",
						"answer": "15",
						"tolerance": 0.01,
						"seed": 2548976
					}
				}
			]
		},
		{
			"name": "Quantitative Methods",
			"children": [
				{
					"name": "Required Rate of Return",
					"children": [
						{
							"name": "Nominal Risk-Free Rate",
							"content": {
								"id": 3,
								"question": "nominal risk-free rate = real risk-free rate + expected inflation rate",
								"answer": "15",
								"tolerance": 0.01,
								"seed": 4235759
							}
						},
						{
							"name": "Required Interest Rate",
							"content": {
								"id": 5,
								"question": "required interest rate = nominal risk-free rate + default risk premium + liquidity, premium + maturity risk premium",
								"answer": "15",
								"tolerance": 0.01,
								"seed": 2548976
							}
						}
					]
				},
				{
					"name": "Effective Annual Rates",
					"content": {
						"id": 5,
						"question": "\\[EAR = (1 + periodic rate)^m - 1\\]",
						"answer": "15",
						"tolerance": 0.01,
						"seed": 2548976
					}
				}
			]
		}
	],
	"questions": [
		{
			"id": 1,
			"seed": 453275,
			"name": "Interest",
			"question": "<p>An account generates interest that varies each period.</p> <p>You are given the balance in the account various times below.</p> <table style=\"width:25%\"> <tr><td>Time</td> <td>\\(0\\)</td> <td>\\(1\\)</td> <td>\\(2\\)</td> <td>\\(3\\)</td></tr> <tr><td>Balance</td> <td>\\([3`RND(30,50,0)`c0]\\)</td><td>\\([4`x3+RND(8,15,0)`c0]\\) </td><td>\\([5`x4+RND(2,6,0)`c0]\\)</td><td>\\(\\$[99`x5+RND(15,25,0)]\\)</td></tr></table>[20`Array(x3,x4,x5,x99)`hide]<p>Calculate the effective rate of interest between time \\([21`RND(0,2,0)]\\) and time \\([22`x21+1]\\)</p>",
			"solution": "\\begin{align*}\n\\class{var1}{i_{t}} &= \\dfrac{\\class{var2}{a(t)} - \\class{var3}{a(t-1)}}{ \\class{var3}{a(t - 1)}}\\\\\n\\\\\n\\class{var1}{i_{[23`x22]}} &= \\dfrac{\\class{var2}{[6`Choose(x20,x22)]} - \\class{var3}{[7`Choose(x20,x21)]} }{\\class{var3}{ [8`x7]}}\\\\\n\\\\\n&= \\class{var1}{[9`ROUND((x6-x7)/x8,4)]} \\hspace{0.1cm} \\text{or} \\hspace{0.1cm}\\class{var1}{[10`x9`p0]}\n\\end{align*}",
			"answer": 10,
			"tolerance": 0.1,
			"placeholder": "r"
		},
		{
			"id": 2,
			"seed": 4532765,
			"name": "Interest",
			"question": "<p>An account generates interest that varies each period.</p> <p>You are given the balance in the account various times below.</p> <table style=\"width:25%\"> <tr><td>Time</td> <td>\\(0\\)</td> <td>\\(1\\)</td> <td>\\(2\\)</td> <td>\\(3\\)</td></tr> <tr><td>Balance</td> <td>\\([3`RND(30,50,0)`c0]\\)</td><td>\\([4`x3+RND(8,15,0)`c0]\\) </td><td>\\([5`x4+RND(2,6,0)`c0]\\)</td><td>\\(\\$[99`x5+RND(15,25,0)]\\)</td></tr></table>[20`Array(x3,x4,x5,x99)`hide]<p>Calculate the effective rate of interest between time \\([21`RND(0,2,0)]\\) and time \\([22`x21+1]\\)</p>",
			"solution": "\\begin{align*}\n\\class{var1}{i_{t}} &= \\dfrac{\\class{var2}{a(t)} - \\class{var3}{a(t-1)}}{ \\class{var3}{a(t - 1)}}\\\\\n\\\\\n\\class{var1}{i_{[23`x22]}} &= \\dfrac{\\class{var2}{[6`Choose(x20,x22)]} - \\class{var3}{[7`Choose(x20,x21)]} }{\\class{var3}{ [8`x7]}}\\\\\n\\\\\n&= \\class{var1}{[9`ROUND((x6-x7)/x8,4)]} \\hspace{0.1cm} \\text{or} \\hspace{0.1cm}\\class{var1}{[10`x9`p0]}\n\\end{align*}",
			"answer": 10,
			"tolerance": 0.1,
			"placeholder": "r"
		}
	],
	"attempts": [
		{
			"id": 5315,
			"ordinal": 1,
			"question": "L1Nom",
			"seed": 4235759,
			"answer": "15.24",
			"tolerance": 0.01,
			"userAnswer": {
				"attempt": "16.24",
				"isCorrect": false
			}
		},
		{
			"id": 5315,
			"ordinal": 1,
			"question": "L1Nom",
			"seed": 4235759,
			"answer": "15.24",
			"tolerance": 0.01,
			"userAnswer": {
				"attempt": "16.24",
				"isCorrect": false
			}
		}
	]
}